<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LikeKnob - Simple, privacy-friendly Like Button on LikeKnob</title>
    <link>https://likeknob.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LikeKnob - Simple, privacy-friendly Like Button on LikeKnob</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 11:00:35 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://likeknob.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Client Library</title>
      <link>https://likeknob.com/docs/client-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 16:56:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://likeknob.com/docs/client-library/</guid>
      <description>To get the most out of LikeKnob, you can take advantages of the advanced configuration object:
Don&amp;rsquo;t know how to design? Don&amp;rsquo;t know how to write JS, HTML or CSS? Contact Me!
var maxWidth = 215 // max width of rating bar and tooltip var defaultOptions = { tooltipMessageWhenRatingAlreadySent: &amp;#39;Already sent!&amp;#39;, tooltipMessageWhenRatingIncomplete: &amp;#39;Specify a Rating first!&amp;#39;, tooltipMessageWhenRatingSent: &amp;#39;Rating sent!&amp;#39;, tooltipMessageWhenSentFailed: &amp;#39;Couldn\&amp;#39;t send rating to server! Could you try again?&amp;#39;, tooltipDisplayInMS: 2500, cssReset: false, question: &amp;#34;What did you not like about this page?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDPR - What we collect from your users</title>
      <link>https://likeknob.com/docs/gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 16:56:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://likeknob.com/docs/gdpr/</guid>
      <description>The General Data Protection Regulation is a law which protects the data and privacy from all EU-citizens.
The answers which your users provide to LikeKnob could be seen as personal data from regulators, so the GDPR also applies to LikeKnob.
What I collect from your users  The rating The answer Parts of the URL (only the pathname, e.g. `/privacy) The date / timestamp when the rating was collected  Where this data is stored The data is store within a european (German) Data Center, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about Privacy Shield and data being exported out of the European Union.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://likeknob.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:58:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://likeknob.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>By using this website and this service, you are agreeing to be bound by this Terms.
A. Definitions  &amp;ldquo;LikeKnob&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; refers to me, the owner, developer and person responsible for this site. The &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo; refers to the applications, dashboards, websites, software, products and services “The User,” “You,” and “Your” refer to the individual person, company, or organization that has visited or is using the Website or Service; that accesses or uses any part of the Account; or that directs the use of the Account in the performance of its functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://likeknob.com/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 12:12:35 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://likeknob.com/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Website Owner and Person responsible for the content according to § 55 RStV Ramon Reschke Durchenbergstr. 13 78315 Radolfzell
E-Mail: hostmaster@likeknob.com Phone: 015678 316796
All the contact information of me given on this website including any photos are explicitly for information purposes or to contact me.
They shall not be used for sending advertisements, spam or the like.
Should this information nevertheless be used for the above-mentioned purposes, I reserve the right to take legal action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://likeknob.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 12:08:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://likeknob.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>I (&amp;ldquo;LikeKnob&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;my&amp;rdquo;) am responsible for the data processing.
This privacy policy applies to all information collected through my websites (such as likeknob.com).
The short version I am using Simple Analytics as a way to see some statistics about my websites. However they don&amp;rsquo;t store or collect any personal data from you. For more information on what Simple Analytics collects (or mostly what they don&amp;rsquo;t collect) click here.
I am not using any tracking cookies nor fingerprinting technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
